big difference
the old habits come back sometimes
the days of ignorance
and I can wash it
a lot of fun outside of those who want
in other names mentioned in his masks
and all messages of God
wants us to say nothing
I'm gonna spend this uh
first football using
a talk
Muhammad gay
Imam honestly Muhammad is one of the
rare people that I believe knows the
truth believes in the truth and his
heart
a struggler
and if you read his writings or or
podcasts
you can see the truth in there some days
he will be as as adventurous as I am it
will come out
with
foreign
this talk could be written by me
but I'm gonna read it without comments
did Muhammad there's one person I am
I'm very happy to get to know I consider
him a friend of mine and I have this
picture
in my office that's how much Allah
God will guide him
if there's no way he would say
and with all the opposition against him
he's been almost Victorious and he's
guaranteed fixed it for as long as he
upholds
and as you know once you see the truth
there is no going back
there's just no way you can go back
after you see the truth
here's what uh what is Muhammad said
let us look at reality not only here but
all over this country
anytime you come together to do some
good you're going to have problems
especially if you're going to make a
good spread
if you're just going to be your private
good maybe you'll last for a while
maybe your last until you die
but if you are doing good and you're
committed and you're going to pass that
good
on to others
so it will grow in numbers you're in
trouble
if you want to get together and do some
wrong you're in the best situation even
the good people won't bother you but if
you want to do good you're in trouble
we have to understand that and that's
the price that the righteous must bear
in the world
you must pay that price except to pay
I know people wouldn't like me when I
made a stand and what they knew what I
stood for
now once did Muhammad not only changed
the Elijah Muhammad system
but he turns it not to Islam as it is
known around the world which response
Islam but he turns into the true Islam
which is a big jump I mean it's a severe
son
so he says I knew people wouldn't like
me when I met the stand and when they
knew what I stood for I knew they
wouldn't like me I knew I was going to
have a whole lot of enemies the more
people knew what I represented I knew
the more enemies I was going to get but
that's the price I accepted to pay
that's the price all of us who want to
do good
have to accept to pay
people aren't going to like you people
are going to make trouble for you people
are going to try to undermine your work
they are going to try to make you lose
faith in each other they try to break
your trust they do anything to defeat
your effort we have to accept that
we don't have to have the CIA the FBI or
the intelligence office of your local
police department do not even need that
there are people out there in the
society who will give you enough help
without those agents
on top of that you have bad elements in
the government some Catholics are so
prejudiced against the religion that
they will sacrifice their time and even
their life to see this religion start in
America
and Protestants who will do the same
then you have some other Islamic groups
that will do the same because they don't
want to see me grow either
so you have the
the FBI the CIA the Israeli intelligence
and the false Muslims and even internal
infiltrations
I'm going I'm not going to name any but
there are some narrow-minded Islamic
groups that will work to defeat you too
because they don't want to see you
prosper either we have to understand
that we have enemies coming at us from
all directions who will do their best to
undermine us a lot of Muslims are not
satisfied with my leadership I'm talking
about Muslims of the world this is
Muhammad
I do believe the great majority of
Muslims on this planet love my
leadership they thanked Allah for my
leadership but we have enough for our
headphones and jealous and dislike us
enough to make trouble
some of them are here in America and
some overseas too we have to understand
these things we have to accept reality
don't think that everybody who comes to
you in this name or in this close is
your friend
it may not be the case your friend is
the one who is truthful who is open
anybody who has to work with you behind
closed doors anybody who has to tell you
something secretly in your ear you
shouldn't trust them
the person who comes out faultly before
the community and lets them
no I am your friend I am a friend of
this community those are the people we
should be inclined to trust but those
persons who stand behind in the back but
never want to be seen up front who claim
to be with us but are whispering things
in our ears don't trust those people I
don't care who they are I don't care
what kind of Applause they come in you
can't trust people like that
we have many masjids all around the
country and all of our measures are
going to be visited our enemies are
already there every Massachusetts
right now I'm talking to people who are
not here to help us they are here to
help us he was talking in the message of
Kansas City by the way
they are working for somebody or some
agent or some agency or they are just
part of the group of prejudiced people
who are against Muslims they are here
just to see that you don't Prosper every
message has them don't think your
message is going to be any different
we're talking to some of them right now
here they are here in case
There's an opportunity where they will
be able to take that advantage to set us
back that is the only purpose in coming
we have to accept that but we don't want
to become paranoid along to the extent
that we're going to say I'm going to
find him no don't try to find him forget
about him just know that he is here but
don't worry about him hope he keeps
coming maybe he'll hear a football that
will change his heart one day
I keep saying that myself
except that he is here and he is a
troublemaker here to see
if he can upset you or take you back or
throw a monkey wrench in your operation
sometimes they just ask a question
behind the good thought
they don't like to see the good spirits
remain we had a good talk
the spirit is high God everyone is going
home in a good spirit
may I ask a question brother Imam what
about so and so and so no I did witness
this myself
just to
what about so and so and so just
to throw a damper on the good spirit
if you read the history of the people
who worked against Prophet Muhammad the
kinds of things they did
they were able to come
to come in and pretend to be a Muslims
the Holy Quran says they would come in
and pretend to be the best of the
Muslims they would establish that they
are the most enthusiastic Muslims they
would say let us go in among them and
establish ourselves as the most
enthusiastic Muslims and then at a
certain time it has just quietly
withdraw
and then that will make everybody wonder
and will break the community of Muslims
the Quran tells us of this scheme they
use and there are many many other
schemes and tricks they use to hurt a
community
make you doubt make you not trust the
community be aware of the many schemes
they work
read the Quran more you have it in
English
translation big thought another good
translation read it in English
translation there
something
don't wait until you learn Arabic now
this is very important I agree with this
don't
wait until you learn Arabic some of you
will never learn Arabic you will die
trying to learn Arabic so so keep
that's right and that's a diversion from
the Quran
so keep trying but in the meantime read
the good English translation of Quran
read it daily don't wait until Ramadan
read it daily become more acquainted
with your holy book so you will know the
tricks that the woman pulls to set back
the good work of the righteous
green
say great Quran more don't wait until
Ramadan read and tell you become more
acquainted with your holy book so you
will know the tricks that the world puts
to set back the good work of the
righteous so he knows the Quran very
well and this is exactly and precisely
why he is guided alhamdulillah never you
never see him talk about it
foreign
footstep oh here's the leader of the
American Muslim mission in Chicago
alhamdulillah
the second football will deal with what
happened last Friday
last Friday we have
a group of people come in this mosque
and ask did you translate verse 239
right or wrong
that was the biggest issue
they asked for some other questions
but you can you can know right away that
the object was not to find the truth
which is our our objective
our objective is to find the truth now
if they would if they were sincerely
seeking the truth
they would call and say brother Rashad
was coming in a couple of weeks
and we want to discuss this issue of
Quran and Hadith and translation
and would like you to prepare and go to
library or do whatever you want to so we
can all help each other find the truth
but they wanted to come secretly
they were telling everybody hush hush
don't tell anybody because we want to go
and embarrass Rashad Khalifa we want to
go they're all objective was to harass
me
embarrass me and to use the quotation
catch him with his pants down
that was the whole objective it was not
to reach the truth
so they come and say it's the
translation of 239 right or wrong
which is a silly question I mean it's
not important if it's right or wrong we
have the Arabic text
also
they were comparing my first edition
with the final edition of some other
translation let's see what we're going
to do right now anyway
you're gonna ask a question like
why were we created
so that's a good question
that is a doctrinal question
why are we here what is the purpose of
our life
these are significant questions not if
239 is translated right or wrong
do they know why they were created
do you know why we are here
because very quickly you know from our
from the appendix on our translation
here
that initially there was God nothing
else not created the engines one of the
engines
ideas he wanted to be a partner with God
this is where the whole thing started
Satan wanted to be a partner with God a
god with God and this is what we're here
for we're here to prove that we worship
God alone without a god with him without
any other partner with him
so that is an important question
so they didn't come here to say
why are we created why are we here
what is the purpose of our life we came
to ask
239 verse 239 was it translated right or
wrong
now what happened last Friday with all
the childish things that went on
is history repeating itself
you know very well they went to the
prophet Muhammad and they said
what do you know about the faces of the
Moon
now did they go why did they go to the
prophet Muhammad to ask what the faces
of the Moon
now Muhammad grew up in a society that
was idle worshiping they were Muslims
according to the religion of Ibrahim
but they they deviated
from the true Islam to idol worship they
worshiped God
perfectly they prayed the five prayers a
day perfectly to Allah
but they also had Annette and manat and
also the other gods with the
Muhammad grew up in that Society
guided him to the worship of God Alone
and he gave me the message so Muhammad
started to utter the message worship God
Alone
what did they do they were up in arms
they attacked him they persecuted him
and now they want to prove that he is
fake
that Muhammad is poor
they don't want to know anything about
the doctrine and the message they said
let us go and prove that he doesn't know
anything he is not a prophet he is faith
that was their purpose
so they go to him and they say listen
Muhammad how to explain that the moon
comes out at the beginning of the month
then and Rising early
and then every day it gets bigger and
later
you know they didn't know about the more
dog out there so any of these things
that we know today but every day in
Saudi Arabia in Mexico they wake up
every morning and then at night there
comes the moon and every day it's
different until it becomes a full moon
then it becomes smaller and later
and they went to Muhammad and said
how do you explain that
what is the objective
we didn't want to know about the phases
of the Moon
you really want to know if 239 is right
or wrong
they want to embarrass somebody and
harass somebody and prove that he is
fake he's brought
they wanted to prove that Muhammad is
fraud
he didn't know about the phases of the
Moon
he didn't want to know about the one God
the Lord's upon God
and
the Quran was written before the
creation of the heavens and the Earth
but the Quran
narrates that story of the people who
went to the prophet Muhammad to prove
that he is fake by asking all the faces
of the Moon
what does this mean folks
this means that these people are setting
peacefully somewhere and then God wanted
them to do something
and all of a sudden they were all kept
up and this God proved that Muhammed is
fake
dad was doing that because it serves the
Muslim Community
it shows them who is who
and it brings things
it brings things to light
and forces certain issues
now I have repeated to them I have
talked to them
what was I talking about
that's right I have emphasized to them
that my translation is an authorized
translation and this of course burned
them and as you know I don't repeat this
kind of thing I'm too embarrassed to say
that
but this is the kind of thing that is
forced by certain by these actions what
I'm saying is that God did it
because it's written in the Quran before
they were born
so they were sitting in Mecca somewhere
and all of a sudden they get the idea
let us go harassment
but it's not really that idea is it
of course there are good candidates for
it
so God wants to force certain issues
I am forced today in this in this foot
but to show you one one reason one of
the reasons why I think this translation
is is authorized and I wouldn't I would
normally be too
embarrassed
to mention
I mentioned it to a couple of you maybe
but uh
it is this kind of Confrontation
that forces out certain issues I'm wrong
I'm going to distribute this to you
okay what I did is I had I have examples
of translations from their favorite
translations
and Pixar
pixel is one of the terrible
translations and I'm going to I'm going
to compare one verse that they have in
their translations and in my translation
over there
and then I would expand to you how I
arrived at Martin's list and why I think
this translation is authorized
well and why it is
you know what I'm a chemist I'm not uh
I'm not an asthma graduate I'm not a
Ireland
and my feeling when I started this
project was I have no business
translating the Quran because everybody
has a copy shared with each other yeah
there's there should be enough problems
here
you have motion yeah
we're going to talk about the
translational verse 22 15. Surah had
verse 15.
and on the top you see the translation
of Albury he was a Harvard man I think
mostly there he thought
um
he's a Cambridge Professor here's his
translation of verse 15. whosoever
thinks God will not help him in the
present world and the world to come let
him stretch up to heaven then let him
sever it and behold whether his Guardian
does away will what enriches him
okay now you know what to do
if you don't think God will support you
in this life and the Hereafter you know
what to do don't you
know the Quran and this is translation
just tell you all you need is treasure
up to heaven
and then separate
and then behold the weather
your guy will pass away with your
whatever age is you this is this is our
police transformation let's go to the
next one
Joseph Ali let's pray together Lucifer
he says if any who thinks if any thing
that God will not help him parenthesis
is Apostle in this world and the
Hereafter let him stretch out around to
the ceiling and cut for instances
himself oh
then let him see whether his plan will
remove that which enrages for instance
is him see now you know better
foreign
this is what you do if you don't think
if you don't think that God will support
him his Apostles in this life and the
Hereafter let's go to the next one this
is the very favorite translation
now we know what to do right
is everybody holding the pixel
translation it says who saw this this
needs some high intellectual
pronunciation
also is one to think parenthesis through
envy that Allah will not give him
parenthesis Muhammad victory in the
world and the Hereafter parenthesis and
is enraged at the thought of his victory
let him stretch the Rope up to the roof
of his dwelling and let him hang himself
excuse me I'd love to translate
and let him hug himself they let him see
whether his strategy the spelling that
that will ask him
laughs
no no this is
this is the advanced question against
the doctrine yes I commit suicide this
is God is saying according to him
[Music]
this is the very favorite translation
I must add here that this is the final
edition of Pixar that's this once they
are comparing with our first edition of
the translation this is the final
nutrition as you know brothers and
sisters we sit here every Friday to
correct my first edition of the
translation our first edition of the
translation
which is by no means person my goodness
and we printed it cheap here and
everything because we know that the
final edition if they really failed they
should translate uh compare my final
translations with the textile private
translation anyway so this is what pixel
says now you know what to do yeah
the next
next translation is sharadi
published under the auspices of
successor of the promised to Messiah and
head of the ahmadia movement is there I
mean the Bible worship right on the
front page
who saw things
that Allah will not help him parenthesis
the prophet in this world and the
Hereafter let him if he can find a way
to heaven and let him cut off the Divine
help then let him see if his device can
remove that which enrages him so now you
really know what to do
all right
okay now we know
who's this Muhammad
okay another translation
the next phase
those who thought that God would never
Grant Victory to Muhammad in this world
nor now Muhammad is Never Enough by the
way
and it has nothing to do with the
prophet Muhammad verse but they
translate everything in terms of
Muhammad he doesn't even bother to put
it in parent and parenthesis
again from the beginning
those who thought that God would never
Grant Victory to Muhammad in this world
nor in the Life Hereafter parenthesis
and now that he is Victorious
parenthesis should hand themselves by
the necks from the ceiling then cut the
stroke that rope Cut the Rope and see if
this can go away with what has and read
them
oh yeah
and red and Rhymes
now now this is a this is
n't even I mean this breaks the doctrine
of Islam of not committing suicide
okay now let's go to uh translation of
the old security here yeah let's see if
it makes sense
if anyone thinks that God cannot support
him in this life as well as in the
Hereafter let him turn totally to God
and several his idolization towards
anyone else you will then find out that
this plan eliminates his morals
this is the solution to any worries that
you have in this world and this
should be consistent with the doctor in
the Quran if anyone of us
does not think that God can support us
here in this world and the Hereafter let
us give
through Islam a tribe let us turn
totally to God and cut out all idol
worship from our lives
and then you will see
that all the Warriors have got no more
headaches no more traffic tickets no
more problems from the spouse the wife
of the husbands
now how did I reach this translation
and this is the world I'm forced by
circumstance to imagine but I considered
one of the signs
that taught me that this translation is
authorized by Allah I do have permission
to translate
the Quran into English what happened
there
it just happened that I started the
translation back in Saint Louis
and when I came to this verse
I finished the 21 sewers
and it was 1971.
and in my house I had a huge table
with all the taxis the Quran and the
translations
that I got my hand on on the table
spread open I turned the patches as I go
with the translation I came to this
verse and I looked up the tafsiers
translated it
if you don't if you don't think that
Muhammad would be victorious in this
life and the Hereafter stretch her off
to the ceiling of the house and hand
yourself to and everybody else took from
him
and of course they didn't make sense to
me
because it defies the doctorates and the
laws of God that you shall not commit
suicide you shall not kill anybody
including yourself
so I left that first blank
I'm saying blessed and God is my witness
I am seeing it in a football
a a worship a practice
of worship and I'm responsible for it
every word in it is true
I left that verse blank and I went to
verse 16.
and they went on
now and then I had to leave for habits
for confidence
now the title of this Surah is
and I finished like about 20 verses
after before